<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Jerry&#39;s Blog</title>
  <subtitle>A Personal Blog</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://jiarui-zhang.com/"/>
  <updated>2017-05-02T12:14:48.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://jiarui-zhang.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Jiarui Zhang</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Think It Real</title>
    <link href="http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/05/02/Think-It-Real/"/>
    <id>http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/05/02/Think-It-Real/</id>
    <published>2017-05-02T12:12:09.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-05-02T12:14:48.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>What you are thinking is not what really happens.<br>This is an episode from <em>Leverage</em> Season 3, hope you can enjoy and think more.<br>&lt;!—-more&gt;</p>
<embed height="415" width="544" quality="high" allowfullscreen="true" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" src="//static.hdslb.com/miniloader.swf" flashvars="aid=3881556&page=39" pluginspage="//www.adobe.com/shockwave/download/download.cgi?P1_Prod_Version=ShockwaveFlash">
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;What you are thinking is not what really happens.&lt;br&gt;This is an episode from &lt;em&gt;Leverage&lt;/em&gt; Season 3, hope you can enjoy and think mor
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Zero" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/Zero/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Academic Field Research 1.5 — Specialism</title>
    <link href="http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/29/Academic-Field-Research-1-5-%E2%80%94-Specialism/"/>
    <id>http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/29/Academic-Field-Research-1-5-—-Specialism/</id>
    <published>2017-04-28T16:06:09.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-04-28T16:08:42.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>THIS RESEARCH IS BASED ON <em>F.R. 1.0</em>, FOR MORE INFORMATION PLEASE VISIT <a href="http://econj.me/2017/04/24/Field-Research-1-0-%E2%80%94-with-ACE-steps/#more" target="_blank" rel="external">Field Research 1.0 — with ACE steps</a>.</strong></p>
<p>In this research, I’d love to put all my attention on the most important area, which was brought up during last Weekly Team Meeting and I poorly answered to.</p>
<p>Because only Alliance Manchester Business School offers a clear course  structure which states there  are 2 routes for prospective students to take, I decide to focus mainly on its specialism routes.</p>
<h2 id=""><a href="#" class="headerlink" title=""></a><a id="more"></a></h2><h4 id="Semester-1"><a href="#Semester-1" class="headerlink" title="Semester 1"></a>Semester 1</h4><p>It’s a semester composed with four mandatory taught course units. Critical Marketing, Marketing Implementation, Marketing and Communications Professional Analysis, Strategic Marketing and New Product Development are all about fundamental theories and principles of marketing.</p>
<hr>
<h4 id="Semester-2"><a href="#Semester-2" class="headerlink" title="Semester 2"></a>Semester 2</h4><p>In Semester 2, we’ve got two routes to choose from. Route 1 is the general route and Route 2 is the specialism route. The major difference between these two is if there is  a core module which makes an elective course compulsory.</p>
<p>There are five specialisms in total, which are B2B, Consumer Behavior, International, Retailing and Services.</p>
<p>After reading into the detailed course description for every single course unit, I think general is better for me.</p>
<p>In a general route, I think I will take Consumer Behavior, e-Business and Digital Technologies for Marketing. These three units can really support my career goal.</p>
<hr>
<h4 id="Summer-Research-and-Dissertation"><a href="#Summer-Research-and-Dissertation" class="headerlink" title="Summer Research and Dissertation"></a>Summer Research and Dissertation</h4><p>I believe I will still want to work for a high-tech company like Apple or Microsoft, especially after taking two semesters’ courses. So the summer research and dissertation must be related to how “e-everything” has changed our life dramatically.</p>
<hr>
<h4 id="Next…"><a href="#Next…" class="headerlink" title="Next…"></a>Next…</h4><ol>
<li>Find and study the text books recommended by the three course unit coordinators, which are as below:</li>
</ol>
<p>Blythe, J. (2014), <em>Consumer Behaviour</em>, 2nd Edition, Sage.</p>
<p>Chaffey, Dave, <em>Digital Business and E-Commerce Management,</em> Pearson Education Ltd, 6th edn, 2014.</p>
<p>Michael J.A. Berry and Gordon S. Linoff, Data Mining Techniques for Marketing, Sales and Customer Relationship Management, Third Edition, John Wiley, 2011</p>
<p>These can enhance my academic background in a way, and help me get a better vision about the program I am going to take.</p>
<ol>
<li>Continue learning Python 3. I’ve already finished the Sololearn Course on <em>Python 3 Tutorial</em>, and got a certificate recognized on LinkedIn.</li>
</ol>
<p><em>Don’t want to miss my lastest post? Get my RSS subscribe now, only at <a href="http://econj.me" target="_blank" rel="external">Jerry’s Blog</a>!</em></p>
<p>​</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THIS RESEARCH IS BASED ON &lt;em&gt;F.R. 1.0&lt;/em&gt;, FOR MORE INFORMATION PLEASE VISIT &lt;a href=&quot;http://econj.me/2017/04/24/Field-Research-1-0-%E2%80%94-with-ACE-steps/#more&quot;&gt;Field Research 1.0 — with ACE steps&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this research, I’d love to put all my attention on the most important area, which was brought up during last Weekly Team Meeting and I poorly answered to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because only Alliance Manchester Business School offers a clear course  structure which states there  are 2 routes for prospective students to take, I decide to focus mainly on its specialism routes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Postgraduate Application" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/Postgraduate-Application/"/>
    
      <category term="Zero" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/Zero/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>ACE — Chap.I Alumni-One</title>
    <link href="http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/27/ACE-%E2%80%94-Chap-I-Alumni-One/"/>
    <id>http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/27/ACE-—-Chap-I-Alumni-One/</id>
    <published>2017-04-27T09:45:49.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-04-27T09:47:21.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi, there! It’s been a few days since my last post. Let’s dig a little deeper for the mostly-positive rated ACE method. Here we’ll start with Alumni.</p>
<a id="more"></a>
<p><strong>It may take around 6 minutes for you to read the following great ideas. If you don’t have that much time, I’m glad to introduce the <em>RSS subscribe</em>, which will be ready when I officially upload this article.</strong></p>
<hr>
<h4 id="Session-One-—-Look-Around-You"><a href="#Session-One-—-Look-Around-You" class="headerlink" title="Session One — Look Around You"></a>Session One — Look Around You</h4><p>Have you really considered yourself as the alumni of your dream schools after reading my <a href="http://econj.me/2017/04/23/ACE%20%E2%80%94%20A%20Quick%20Method%20for%20Postgraduate%20Applicants%20Orientation/#more" target="_blank" rel="external"><em>Introduction To ACE</em></a>? You may have a bunch of interesting people in your mind, dreaming of becoming one of them. But after a super wonderful workshop meeting, new ideas just flushed in. And this seems to be a better beginning for the whole ACE process — Just take a break and look around you.</p>
<p>Do you know them? I bet you know some. Pick up one randomly and think one critical question: What is his/her occupation? A professor? A manager? A housekeeper? A waiter? A policewoman…? This works best if you are doing your internship. </p>
<ol>
<li><strong>Take</strong> your courage, step forward, show your smile and ask him/her “where did you graduate from?” After knowing his/her legendary life course, you may find the major he/she took doesn’t fit with what he/she is doing. You may find dozens of turning points stats with “I could have, you know”, remember them.</li>
<li><strong>Repeat</strong> the last process again and again with 10 different people you are familiar with, make sure they will share the true life tracks with you. </li>
<li><strong>Review</strong> the precious information you’ve collected. Find those who have the least turning points, talk to them again. Ask them one last question: Are you happy with your job?</li>
</ol>
<p>You must have noticed that I didn’t mention about specific professions no more. The reason is obvious, you are only starting to recognize some alumni. I don’t know what conclusion you may get, but I’m sure you must have got the primary impression of the invisible link between major and work. </p>
<p>During this session, two advice should be taken into consideration.</p>
<p>(1) Do not argue because the 10 people you find is of great limitation, they are who you are.</p>
<p>(2) Do not find too many of them with the same occupation and same level of studying, regardless your potential profession and level degree. Just remember, this is for general.</p>
<hr>
<p>What’s your great findings? Share with me now! Do you still believe the alumni really matters? Are those with a higher education more stable when choosing their jobs? Are they deeply affected by their schools? Who do you want to be alumnus with? Do you still have faith in your dream school or preferred major?</p>
<p><strong>You Are Contributing!</strong></p>
<p>If there’s any confusion or suggestion, please do email me at zhangjr@email.cufe.edu.cn, let’s develop the open-source theory together! </p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;Hi, there! It’s been a few days since my last post. Let’s dig a little deeper for the mostly-positive rated ACE method. Here we’ll start with Alumni.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Postgraduate Application" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/Postgraduate-Application/"/>
    
      <category term="One" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/One/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Field Research 1.0 — with ACE steps</title>
    <link href="http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/24/Field-Research-1-0-%E2%80%94-with-ACE-steps/"/>
    <id>http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/24/Field-Research-1-0-—-with-ACE-steps/</id>
    <published>2017-04-24T08:19:41.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-04-24T08:24:22.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is a research about my own application plan, using very basic ACE method.<br><a id="more"></a></p>
<h4 id="Alumni"><a href="#Alumni" class="headerlink" title="Alumni"></a>Alumni</h4><p><strong>Target Filter</strong></p>
<ol>
<li>Target Company: Apple, Microsoft, Google, Amazon, HTC, Tencent, Valve Corporation, Bilzzard Entertainment</li>
<li>Target Industry: Internet, Retail, Entertainment</li>
<li>Target Position: Marketing Strategy, Sales, Business Development</li>
<li>Target School: University of Manchester, King’s College London, University of Lancaster</li>
<li>Working Language: English, Chinese</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Linkedin Result</strong></p>
<ol>
<li><p>Total Employee: 240 people</p>
</li>
<li><p>Sub-total Stat.</p>
</li>
</ol>
<table>
<thead>
<tr>
<th style="text-align:center">University</th>
<th style="text-align:center">Employee</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td style="text-align:center">Manchester</td>
<td style="text-align:center">99</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="text-align:center">KCL</td>
<td style="text-align:center">79</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td style="text-align:center">Lancaster</td>
<td style="text-align:center">62</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<ol>
<li>Summary: My target schools are qualified for my career plan.</li>
</ol>
<hr>
<h4 id="Condition-—-For-Taught-Master’s"><a href="#Condition-—-For-Taught-Master’s" class="headerlink" title="Condition — For Taught Master’s"></a>Condition — For Taught Master’s</h4><p>Target Degree: MSc in Marketing/ International Marketing</p>
<ul>
<li><h5 id="University-of-Manchester"><a href="#University-of-Manchester" class="headerlink" title="University of Manchester"></a>University of Manchester</h5></li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li><p>Duration: 12 months, Full-time</p>
</li>
<li><p>Fees: £20,500 per annum</p>
</li>
<li><p>Entry Requirements:</p>
</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li><p>IELTS: 7.0 overall with speaking and writing 6.5 and no other element below 6.0</p>
</li>
<li><p>iBT: 100 overall with a minimum score of 22 in writing and speaking, and 21 in reading and listening</p>
</li>
<li><p>Academic: 4 year Bachelor degree with a minimum average of between 82-90% from a well ranked institution</p>
</li>
<li><p>Course Details: </p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="http://www.mbs.ac.uk/masters/_assets/pdf/2016/marketing-structure-2016.pdf" target="_blank" rel="external">For detailed Course Structure @ UM</a></p>
<ul>
<li><h5 id="King’s-College-London"><a href="#King’s-College-London" class="headerlink" title="King’s College London"></a>King’s College London</h5></li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li><p>Duration: 12 months, Full-time</p>
</li>
<li><p>Fees: £25,950 per annum</p>
</li>
<li><p>Entry Requirements:</p>
</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li><p>IELTS: 7.0 overall with a minimum of 6.5 in each skill (Band B)</p>
</li>
<li><p>iBT: 100 overall with a minimum of 25 in writing and 23  in each of the other skills (Band B)</p>
</li>
<li><p>Academic: 4 year Bachelor degree with a minimum average of between 80-88% from a <em>Chinese Universitiy considered Prestigious (Project 211)</em></p>
</li>
<li><p>Course Details: </p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="http://www.kcl.ac.uk/study/postgraduate/taught-courses/international-marketing-msc.aspx" target="_blank" rel="external">For detailed Courese Structure @KCL</a></p>
<ul>
<li><h5 id="University-of-Lancaster"><a href="#University-of-Lancaster" class="headerlink" title="University of Lancaster"></a>University of Lancaster</h5></li>
</ul>
<ol>
<li><p>Duration: 12 months, Full-time</p>
</li>
<li><p>Fees: £21,000 per annum</p>
</li>
<li><p>Entry Requirements:</p>
</li>
</ol>
<ul>
<li><p>IELTS: 7.0, with at least 6.0 in each element</p>
</li>
<li><p>iBT: 100 (with minimum 22 in each skill)</p>
</li>
<li><p>Academic: Applicants are expected to hold a good degree in any discipline other than marketing. An Upper Second Class honours, or 3.2 GPA on a 4-point scale or an average of B+ are all considered to be a ‘good degree’</p>
</li>
<li><p>Course Details: </p>
</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="http://www.lancaster.ac.uk/lums/study/masters/programmes/marketing-msc/programme-content/" target="_blank" rel="external">For detailed Programme Content @LUMS</a></p>
<hr>
<h4 id="Engagement"><a href="#Engagement" class="headerlink" title="Engagement"></a>Engagement</h4><p>After the field research into the MSc in Marketing seems that they do not require the applicants with strong academic background in marketing.  Even LUMS pointed out that this course is specially designed for those who are not marketing graduates. </p>
<p>However, I believe it’s better to emphasize on my internship and business related experience as well as get my marketing academic background recognized.</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;This is a research about my own application plan, using very basic ACE method.&lt;br&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Postgraduate Application" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/Postgraduate-Application/"/>
    
      <category term="One" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/One/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>ACE — A Quick Method for Postgraduate Applicants Orientation</title>
    <link href="http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/23/ACE%20%E2%80%94%20A%20Quick%20Method%20for%20Postgraduate%20Applicants%20Orientation/"/>
    <id>http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/23/ACE — A Quick Method for Postgraduate Applicants Orientation/</id>
    <published>2017-04-23T14:42:55.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-04-23T15:39:07.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Introduction</p>
<p>Hello there! I don’t know how you find this blog, but hey, if you are applying postgraduate programs, 5 minutes is all you need to know everything about The ACE Method, which I am developing to aid those who is or will be struggling like me.<br><a id="more"></a><br>The ACE stands for 3 simple words: Alumni, Condition and Engagement. And this is also just the 3 steps for you to take in order.</p>
<ol>
<li>Alumni. Don’t be surprised, think ahead is of vital importance for you. No matter which program you want to take, you’ll inevitably become a potential famous alumni. Especially for those porgrams which only last for 1 year or 2, they may expect very little from you in such a short time. However, you are earmarked with “John Doe’s School” forever. In this step, you need to have a relatively clear career plan. Then you should find those who fits your career goal on “Linkedin Like” websites, to see where are they come from and their “alumni property”. In this way, you’ll get a list of “Target Schools (Unfiltered)”.</li>
<li>Condition. Looking at the spreadsheet you’ve just generated, you may find some schools are not reliable, such as a business school loacted in Pyongyang. Delete those you don’t like, according to  whatever reasons you like, it’s your own application anyway. Leave no more than 15 schools on the “Target Schools (Filtered)” list. Then look into those schools after your selection, find the basic conditions for admission. Remember, you may achieve your career goal by taking a variety of independent programs, and they probably have different conditions, just make sure you’ve grasped every single opportunities! Obviously, next you need to compare your own condition with the requirements: GPA, internship experience, academic backgroud, iBT, IELTS etc..<br><strong>Attention!</strong> <em>This is called CONDITION for a reason, because you may get a CONDITIONAL OFFER from any school, so don’t be upset when you find the requirements published are a little too high. You can be the next exception!</em></li>
<li>Engagement.<br>This is the easiest part, but can also be a little tricky if you are not determined. “1+2=3” is easy, but if I ask you to add from 1 to a certain number, which I won’t tell you, only with your bare hands is not something easy to do. It’s just like self-exploring, you can do one step easily and know better about yourself. However, you can still dig one-step deeper, not knowing the exact depth. When you start the draft of your PS, you need to show your engagement in the area, the school, even the whole industry. The thing is, you cannot discover your engagement unless you know yourself very well. It’s like buying some everyday goods or services for free, you must show your sponsor you are buying it for a reason, and you can maximize its utility. Thus, get yourself engaged in the program before your application and prepare a perfect to impress the admission officers!</li>
</ol>
<p>Thank you for staying with me, are you interested in this ACE method? This is acutally derived from my last post article <em>Why I Am Qualified for Manchester?</em>, and it’s merely a brief introduction, there will be a series of following updates which can provide much more detailed information about every step. And I might post some problems I met during my applicaitonand its solutions. This blog will be updated at least once a week, but I’ll check the comments every day. So leave your comments below or just email me at zhangjr@email.cufe.edu.cn (in case you may have limited access to Disqus).</p>
<p>Looking forward to hearing from you lovely guys!</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;Introduction&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello there! I don’t know how you find this blog, but hey, if you are applying postgraduate programs, 5 minutes is all you need to know everything about The ACE Method, which I am developing to aid those who is or will be struggling like me.&lt;br&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Postgraduate Application" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/Postgraduate-Application/"/>
    
      <category term="One" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/One/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why I am qualified for Manchester</title>
    <link href="http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/21/Why%20I%20am%20qualified%20for%20Manchester/"/>
    <id>http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/21/Why I am qualified for Manchester/</id>
    <published>2017-04-21T09:45:49.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-04-23T15:13:32.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This self-proving process is painstaking <em>(which means this will be updated occasionally)</em>.</p>
<p>From my point of view, there are three reletively independent parts for a qualification, which in short is TEA.<br><a id="more"></a></p>
<ol>
<li>Ticket</li>
</ol>
<p>The first thing for me is to give the addmissions officers a strong reason to click open my CV and resume. The basic supporting material is the ticket to next step. GPA, IELTS or iBT, recommendation letters and a related academic background. After ticking the requirment spreadsheet, luckily, I think I’ve got it right. However, a ticket is not a guarantee.</p>
<ol>
<li>Engagement</li>
</ol>
<p>“You never know if you’ll fit in the university until you really study here.” That’s what Professor Simons told me, when I attended the Cambridge Academic Development Seminar two years ago.</p>
<p>Frankly speaking, I’ve never been to Manchester, and unfortunately, I was a big fan of Chelsea F.C.. But I do know that Manchester is the second-most poplulous urban area. Bingo! Apart from London, this must be the best place for a Business School student. </p>
<p>“Why do a business postgraduate program? “ ,asked myself. I believe this is an important question held by the admissions officers as well. I’d say this internship I am doing now, at HTC Vive China Sales Team, firmed my decision. I never thought I would so enjoy working at a high-tech company. Selling my favorite product is what I’d love to do. As you know from my self-introduction, I am a gamer and an Apple fan, so I’m considering working for Blizzard, Apple or back to HTC Vive. </p>
<p>With a clear goal and related experience, I’m sure I can persuade Manchester that I’m worth it.</p>
<ol>
<li>Alumni</li>
</ol>
<p>There’s one more thing I’d like to consider, which is after graduation affairs. By thinking of thiese, I can show Manchester that I’m confident enough to get enrolled. And under the guidance of a specific goal, I will make a contribution to this entity. As my supervisor told me on my first day: you need to keep a clear mind about you contirbution before you ask for resources from the organization.</p>
<p>Jerry</p>
<p>04.21</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;This self-proving process is painstaking &lt;em&gt;(which means this will be updated occasionally)&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From my point of view, there are three reletively independent parts for a qualification, which in short is TEA.&lt;br&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Postgraduate Application" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/Postgraduate-Application/"/>
    
      <category term="One" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/One/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>The First Step of Hexo</title>
    <link href="http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/19/The%20First%20Step%20of%20Hexo/"/>
    <id>http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/19/The First Step of Hexo/</id>
    <published>2017-04-19T10:57:14.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-04-23T15:13:15.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi! Welcome to my official Blog at Hexo!<br>Today, I’ll be trying to apply a postgraduate program in UK.<br>So, you may find the whole record of my Applying Life!<br>And I’ll also post some python related articles~<br>P.S. Really love Markdown.<br><a id="more"></a><br>And here comes the first article, a reply on the forum.</p>
<ol>
<li>I do have a new sense about applying a postgraduate program overseas. At the very beginning, I tried so hard digging all the requirements for admission, such as GPA, IELTS, GMAT etc.. And the first two steps(It’s a pity I only got time to finish the first two, due to IELTS test coming up this Sat. and internship work.) enlightened me that there exists something cannot be examined quantitively. My grade is a vital component in my application, but no all.<br>And taking my postgraduate program overseas is not like competing with all the applicants with scoring ability, but to show the school that I AM QUALIFIED. And here goes another question: What is the standard of QUALIFIED? I’m not sure at this very moment, however, I’ll update HERE once the idea bumps up(too many DDLs crowding recently).</li>
<li>Why do I have to take postgraduate programs overseas? The answer is obvious: for future career development. It’s a must-do to have a Master degree if you want to go further and get paid better. I’m trying to apply a Marketing related program, mostly because of the internship at HTC Vive. The first day I reported to my director, I got my hands dirty on dealing with orders flying from all over the country. I feel so lucky to have the opportunity to be the member of China Sales Team.<br>One of my strengths is the ability to learn something new, but it also leads to my worst weakness: NEVER DIG DEEP. So how to maximize the utility of this life I got 22 years ago? Dealing with different people on different things by different rules in different fields. That’s something keeps me curious enough to breathe.<br>And Marketing is related to the major, Public Finance, I am studying. They all want to predict the human behavior and take advantage of their prediction(mostly guess). I’m so addicted to this as well.<br>In the last, when I looked back on what I’d done during the two and half years in college, I suddenly found myself winning awards related to BUSINESS(which kept me BUSY). These can be used as supporting materials, of course, to get a better chance get myself admitted. However, aren’t they indicating that’s what I like and am good at?</li>
</ol>
<p>Jerry<br>April.19</p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;Hi! Welcome to my official Blog at Hexo!&lt;br&gt;Today, I’ll be trying to apply a postgraduate program in UK.&lt;br&gt;So, you may find the whole record of my Applying Life!&lt;br&gt;And I’ll also post some python related articles~&lt;br&gt;P.S. Really love Markdown.&lt;br&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Postgraduate Application" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/Postgraduate-Application/"/>
    
      <category term="Zero" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/Zero/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hello World</title>
    <link href="http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/19/hello-world/"/>
    <id>http://jiarui-zhang.com/2017/04/19/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2017-04-19T10:50:32.000Z</published>
    <updated>2017-04-23T15:12:44.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to <a href="https://hexo.io/" target="_blank" rel="external">Hexo</a>! This is your very first post. Check <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/" target="_blank" rel="external">documentation</a> for more info. If you get any problems when using Hexo, you can find the answer in <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/troubleshooting.html" target="_blank" rel="external">troubleshooting</a> or you can ask me on <a href="https://github.com/hexojs/hexo/issues" target="_blank" rel="external">GitHub</a>.<br><a id="more"></a></p>
<h2 id="Quick-Start"><a href="#Quick-Start" class="headerlink" title="Quick Start"></a>Quick Start</h2><h3 id="Create-a-new-post"><a href="#Create-a-new-post" class="headerlink" title="Create a new post"></a>Create a new post</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><div class="line">1</div></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><div class="line">$ hexo new <span class="string">"My New Post"</span></div></pre></td></tr></table></figure>
<p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/writing.html" target="_blank" rel="external">Writing</a></p>
<h3 id="Run-server"><a href="#Run-server" class="headerlink" title="Run server"></a>Run server</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><div class="line">1</div></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><div class="line">$ hexo server</div></pre></td></tr></table></figure>
<p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/server.html" target="_blank" rel="external">Server</a></p>
<h3 id="Generate-static-files"><a href="#Generate-static-files" class="headerlink" title="Generate static files"></a>Generate static files</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><div class="line">1</div></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><div class="line">$ hexo generate</div></pre></td></tr></table></figure>
<p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/generating.html" target="_blank" rel="external">Generating</a></p>
<h3 id="Deploy-to-remote-sites"><a href="#Deploy-to-remote-sites" class="headerlink" title="Deploy to remote sites"></a>Deploy to remote sites</h3><figure class="highlight bash"><table><tr><td class="gutter"><pre><div class="line">1</div></pre></td><td class="code"><pre><div class="line">$ hexo deploy</div></pre></td></tr></table></figure>
<p>More info: <a href="https://hexo.io/docs/deployment.html" target="_blank" rel="external">Deployment</a></p>
]]></content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;Welcome to &lt;a href=&quot;https://hexo.io/&quot;&gt;Hexo&lt;/a&gt;! This is your very first post. Check &lt;a href=&quot;https://hexo.io/docs/&quot;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more info. If you get any problems when using Hexo, you can find the answer in &lt;a href=&quot;https://hexo.io/docs/troubleshooting.html&quot;&gt;troubleshooting&lt;/a&gt; or you can ask me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/hexojs/hexo/issues&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
    
    </summary>
    
    
      <category term="Zero" scheme="http://jiarui-zhang.com/tags/Zero/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
